almanhal.com 2019-05-17

# Al Manhal | Privacy Policy

The following documents represent the privacy policy for all products & services associated with Al Manhal as well as the Al Manhal website:

**ALMANHAL  
PRODUCTS AND SERVICES PRIVACY POLICY**

LAST UPDATED: May 25, 2018

Al Manhal FZLLC and its applicable subsidiaries (collectively, “ **Al Manhal** ” or “ **we** ” or “ **us** ” or“ **our** ”)* respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy.

Al Manhal wants you to have a positive experience in connection with our products and services. We want you to know that we respect the privacy and security of our users. Our goal is to provide you with an experience that delivers the information, resources and services that are helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we may collect information from you. We discuss our information collection practices below.This Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy principles we follow, in accordance with our operations.

This Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy practices with respect to your information when you use our software, mobile applications and other products or services (“ **Services** ”). If you do not agree to these terms, do not use the Services.

For any questions on this Privacy Policy or our data practices, or to send in a data subject access request, you can contact us using one of the following methods:  

  1. _Via Mail:_  Al Manhal FZLLC.  
Office 106, Bldg 25, Dubai Healthcare City  
PO Box 505159  
Dubai, United Arab Emirates  
Attn: General Counsel  

  2. _Via Email:_  [privacy@almanhal.com](mailto:privacy@almanhal.com) _  
  
_

*For a list of Data Protection Representatives see the table at the end of this Privacy Policy.

**What Information Is Collected and How is it Used?**

**[Information about Children's Areas at Section H of this Policy]**

**A.     What Information Do We Collect?**

**1\. Personal Information:  **information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual, including: name, title, date of birth, unique identifier (e.g., account number), company name, job function, expertise,postal address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, geolocation, certain device information, and IP address. If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with our Services, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**2\. Non-Personal Information:   **any information that does not reveal your identity or does not relate to an identifiable individual. This might include anonymous identifiers and information, analytics and usage information, non-precise geolocation, and web server log files to track Website trends, administer the Website, and gather demographic information. 

**B.    How Do We Collect the Information?**

We only collect and use Personal Information when you voluntarily provide it to us or when an institutional customer provides it to us in connection with its method of authenticating users for access to our Services, with the exception of your IP address which may be automatically captured when you access our Services. Under limited circumstances, we also collect limited business contact information from legitimate third parties.

In order to use some of the unique functions within our Services, a user must first complete a registration form or provide an email address that will require the user’s disclosure of limited Personal Information. Such disclosure is strictly voluntary. In addition, and in order to contact us by email, however, you must provide an email address.

We automatically collect non-Personal Information, generated from your use of our Services. We use this non-Personal Information in the aggregate. We do not combine these types of non-Personal Information with Personal Information.

**Cookies:**  Al Manhal and our third-party partners may place a "cookie" or other tracking or information gathering device used in the industry in the browser files of a user's computer. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user'shard drive containing information about the user.  We use cookies to collect information about your use of our Services, which enable us to track and target the interests of our users.  We then use that information to solely enhance the user’s experience within our Services.  We also use cookies from third-parties for analytics purposes.  Third-party cookies are covered by the third-party’s privacy policy.

Users can set their browsers or third-party software to reject cookies. The means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, so we recommend you visit your browser's help menu for more information. Please note that if a user rejects or disables certain cookies, the user may be unable to use portions of our Services. Some of the third-party websites we provide links to also may use cookies. We have no control over these linked websites or access to or control over cookies or other technology used by linked websites.

The following is a list of the cookies that may be used in some or all of the Services:

**Type**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
Essential

| 

We use these strictly necessary cookies to provide you with services available through our Services and to use some of its features.  
  
Preference

| 

We use these cookies to remember your settings and preferences.  
  
Security

| 

We use these cookies to authenticate users and help identify and prevent security risks.  
  
Performance

| 

We use these cookies to collect information about how you interact with our Services and to help us improve them.  
  
**Product**

| 

**Type and Name**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
All Products

| 

Analytics Cookie from Google Analytics

| 

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects aggregate statistical data about how visitors use the Websites (i.e., what pages users visit, how long they are on the Websites, how they got there and what they click on) so that we can improve the user experience and serve up the content our visitors find most useful. 

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its analytics service at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) _._    
  
Google also offers a tool that allows you to opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites and can be found [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).   
  
All Products

| 

Advertising Cookie from Google Adwords

| 

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects data about your activities within the Services to provide you targeted advertising, but does not personally or directly identify you.  

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its advertising features at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

You can opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). You can also opt out with [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCjR4sMQxSJOzB_v8TNsRdxQm9IOWavuDzrTGX3ANa8kqL6ITAuvJTz80Gcsh_l-z6OoMveMxAUAhfjoO1OxDTVkXfwPgey3tRsdJsgMeZ6oDRf0Wb8&hl=en) or the [NAI’s consumer opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed).  
  
**C.    How Do We Use the Information?**

We use the Personal Information we collect for the limited purposes of processing your transactions, establishing the identity of account holders, customer service, authorization, customer support, content processing, content classification, and providing you with information concerning our Services. We will retain this information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you Services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

For example, our Bookshelf service employs a personalization feature that requires completion of a registration form before a user can use that feature. The personalization feature of the Bookshelf is a powerful tool that provides users with the means to create and save histories of searches they have conducted. We believe the personalization feature is a useful tool that will enhance the user's experience at the site, but it does require the user to provide Personal Information to us.

We use the non-Personal Information we collect to administer the Services, perform diagnostics, collect content-specific usage statistics, protect the Services and their content from inappropriate use, and improve the user's experience.

We may use the Personal Information and non-Personal Information we collect by sharing it with third-party agents,vendors, contractors, partners, or content providers of Al Manhal (collectively, "Contractors") for purposes of managing purchases of our products and services, servicing our systems, and obtaining support services for our businesses. We are not in the business of selling Personal Information to third-parties or Contractors, and will share it with Contractors only as we describe in this Privacy Policy. In situations where we provide Personal Information to Contractors, we ensure access is granted to the Contractors only upon the condition that the Personal Information is kept confidential and is used only for carrying out the services these Contractors are performing for Al Manhal. As part of making that determination whether we will provide Personal Information to Contractors, we will obtain assurances that they will appropriately safeguard Personal Information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

The Personal Information we collect from you may be transferred to, and processed in, countries other than the country in which you live. These countries may have data protection laws that are different to the laws of your country. Specifically, the servers we use to provide our Services are located in the United States. This means that when we collect your Personal Information, we may process it in the United States or the country where you live. However, when we process your Personal Information,irrelevant of its processing location, we take appropriate safeguards, as discussed below, to require that your Personal Information remains protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may share your usage data related to our Services with our affiliates for purposes of providing or improving our Services. We will not disclose any information about your usage data related to our Services to unaffiliated third-parties, except as necessary to enhance the product experience, service the legal agreement between us and your employer or affiliated institution under which you are provided access to our Services, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our contractual obligations to report aggregated usage data to content providers, or as required by law.

We also reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information if we are required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, and to the extent permitted by applicable local law, to respond to claims, or to protect or advance the rights, property, safety, or well-being of our company, our employees, customers, or the public.

We will not use your Personal Information for automated-decision making.

In the unlikely event that all or substantially all of the assets of Al Manhal are acquired, customer information, which may include Personal Information, maybe one of the transferred assets unless restricted by applicable local law.

**D.    What is our legal basis for collecting and using your Personal Information? (EEA Only)**

Our legal basis for collecting and using the Personal Information described above will depend on the Personal Information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect Personal Information from you only (i) where we need the Personal Information to perform a contract with you or your organization, (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms, or (iii) where we have your consent to do so.In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect Personal Information from you or may otherwise need the Personal Information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.

If we ask you to provide Personal Information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with your institution, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your Personal Information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible impact if you do not provide your Personal Information).

Similarly, if we collect and use your Personal Information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your Personal Information, please contact us using the contact information provided above.

**E.    How Do We Secure Personal Information?**

Al Manhal has taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure that Personal Information we have collected or will collect in the future is secure. For example, we have limited the number of people who have access to Personal Information, by electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. As a reminder, Al Manhal provides links to third-party websites. These websites may not have the same privacy policies as Al Manhal. We take  reasonable care in recommending these websites but we are not responsible for their content or privacy policies. We urge users to read the privacy statement of a third-party website when leaving our Services and linking to a third-party website.

We always use industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data we receive.  We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you in connection with our Services.

**F.    How Can I Access, Correct, Amend or Remove Information About Me, etc.?**

We want to assure you that you have access to your Personal Information that we collect and store. Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may contact us using the contact information stated above to exercise the following rights:

  * Access your data to check and review them;
  * Have a copy of your Personal Information;
  * Demand that we supplement, correct or delete your Personal Information; or cease or restrict the collection, processing, use or disclosure of your Personal Information; the right of rectification will comprise the right to have incomplete Personal Information completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement;
  * Object to the processing of your Personal Information;
  * Receive your Personal Information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have it transmitted to another controller; provided that the processing is based on your respective consent or to execute a contractual relationship or a relationship prior to entering into contract with you.; and
  * Withdraw your consent where the Personal Information we collect from you is based on your consent.

We will respond to your request within thirty(30) days of receipt.

If you have granted consent, you can withdraw your consent at any time with future effect. Please address your withdrawal by contacting us in writing or by email at the contact information stated above.  

If you are located in the EU, after May 25,2018, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in relation to the processing of your Personal Information.

**G.   What Choices Do I Have?**

We understand that you may not want to allow our disclosure of your Personal Information to our Contractors, or to let us use that information for purposes that you believe may be incompatible with the purpose for which it originally was collected (as permitted by this Privacy Policy) or that you later may authorize. Therefore, you may contact us to inform us that you do not want to permit these uses of your Personal Information. To do so, please contact us using the contact information provided above.

It is important to us that the Personal Information we collect is appropriate and relevant to the purposes for which we intend to use it. We will use Personal Information only in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the person providing the information. Al Manhal will take reasonable steps to ensure that Personal Information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.

You may sign-up to receive email newsletters or other marketing materials from us. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may immediately update your email preferences free of cost by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you or at your account settings on our website or by contacting us at [privacy@almanhal.com](mailto:privacy@almanhal.com).

**H.     Collection and Use of Information from Children: Information for Parents**

Most of our Services are not directed toward children. For our Services that are designed to be used by children under Age 16, if a user under Age 16 wants to use our personalization features, we ask the user to register with their first name and a random, user-generated, unique identifier only.

If you are a parent and have questions about our practices, please feel free to contact us using the contact information listed above.

**I.     How Long Do We Retain This Information?**

We retain Personal Information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business interest or other legal need todo so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax or accounting requirements).

When we have no further legitimate business interest or legal need to process your Personal Information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your Personal Information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**J.     What Are My Rights?**

Upon request, Al Manhal will tell you if we process any of your Personal Information. Depending on your country of residency, you may have legal rights with respect to your Personal Information.As such, if you would like to manage, change, limit, or delete your Personal Information, you can do so via the account settings or by contacting us using the information provided above. We will respond to your request within are reasonable time frame.

If we process your Personal Information based on our legitimate interests, you can object to this processing in certain circumstances. In such cases, we will cease processing your Personal Information unless we have compelling legitimate grounds to continue processing or where it is needed for compliance and/or legal reasons. Where we use your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes, you can always object or opt out by using the “Unsubscribe” link in found in emails we send to you or by contacting us at [privacy@almanhal.com](mailto:privacy@almanhal.com).

**Questions**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our practices, please use the contact information found at that page or listed above.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We will notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy by posting an updated policy on this page. You acknowledge that any use of our Services is based on this Privacy Policy, current at the time of use.  If we make any material changes, we will notify you by means of a notice via the Services prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**EEA Data Protection Representatives**

**_Al Manhal Data Protection Representative_**

| 

**_Country of Business Registration_**  
  
---|---  
  
[to be inserted]

| 

[to be inserted]  
  
**ALMANHAL  
WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

LAST UPDATED: May 25, 2018

Al Manhal FZ LLC and its applicable subsidiaries (collectively, “ **Al Manhal** ” or “ **we** ” or “ **us** ” or“ **our** ”)* respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy.

Al Manhal wants you to have a positive experience at the websites we operate. We want you to know that we respect the privacy and security of our users. Our goal is to provide you with an experience that delivers the information, resources and services that are helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we may collect information from you. We discuss our information collection practices below. This Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy principles we follow, in accordance with our operations.

This Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy practices in effect at Al Manhal’s websites, including our Careers Site [https://www.almanhal.com/en/Page/Careers](https://www.almanhal.com/en/Page/Careers%20) (the “ **Websites** ”) and information gathered when you initiate requests for information regarding our products or services.  The Websites do not include those sites which host our products, services and applications, which are governed by their own privacy policies.  If you do not agree to these terms, do not access these Websites.

For any questions on this Privacy Policy or our data practices, or to send in a data subject access request, you can contact us using one of the following methods:

  1. _Via Mail:_  Al Manhal FZLLC  
Office 106, Bldg 25, Dubai Healthcare City  
PO Box 505159  
Dubai, United Arab Emirates  
Attn: General Counsel  

  2. _Via Email:_  [privacy@almanhal.com](mailto:privacy@almanhal.com)

*For a list of Data Protection Representatives see the table at the end of this Privacy Policy.

**What Information Is Collected and How is it Used?**

**[Information about Children's Areas at Section H of this Policy]**

**A.     What Information Do We Collect?**

**1\. Personal Information:  **information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual, including: name, title, company name, job function,expertise, postal address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, geolocation, certain device information, and IP address. In addition, our Careers Site collects the following Personal Information that you provide us in the job application process: employment history; resume or CV;education history; and sensitive and/or demographic information such as gender,information about your citizenship and/or nationality, medical or health information and/or your racial or ethnic origin. If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**2\. Non-Personal Information:   **any information that does not reveal your identity or does not relate to an identifiable individual.This might include anonymous identifiers and information, analytics and usage information, non-precise geolocation, and web server log files to track Website trends, administer the Website, and gather demographic information.

**B.    How Do We Collect the Information?**

We only collect and use Personal Information when you voluntarily provide it to us, with the exception of your geolocation and IP address which may be automatically captured when you access our Websites. In order to use some portions of our Websites, a user must first complete a registration form or provide an e-mail address that will require disclosure of Personal Information. In addition, in order to apply for employment with Al Manhal, you will have to disclose Personal Information regarding your identity and employment history. Such disclosure is strictly voluntary. In order to contact us by e-mail, however, you must provide an e-mail address.

We automatically collect non-Personal Information, generated from your use of our Websites. We use this non-Personal Information in the aggregate. We do not combine these types of non-Personal Information with Personal Information. We may also share aggregated demographic information with our business partners and companies that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with Al Manhal.

**Cookies:**  We may place a "cookie" or other tracking or information gathering device used in the industry in the browser files of a user's computer. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.  We use cookies to collect information about your use of our Websites, which enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Websites.  We also use cookies from third parties for marketing purposes (such as interest-based online advertising) that allow us to display Al Manhal promotional material to you on other sites you visit across the internet partners based on your visit to our Websites.Third-party cookies are covered by the third-party’s privacy policy.

Users can set their browsers or third party software to reject cookies. The means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, so we recommend you visit your browser's help menu for more information. Please note that if a user rejects or disables certain cookies, the user may be unable to use portions of our Website. Some of the third-party websites we provide links to also may use cookies. We have no control over these linked Websites or access to or control over cookies or other technology used by linked websites.

The following is a list of the cookies that may be used in some or all of the Services:

**Type**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
Essential

| 

We use these strictly necessary cookies to provide you with services available through our Services and to use some of its features.  
  
Preference

| 

We use these cookies to remember your settings and preferences.  
  
Security

| 

We use these cookies to authenticate users and help identify and prevent security risks.  
  
Performance

| 

We use these cookies to collect information about how you interact with our Services and to help us improve them.  
  
In addition, some of our Websites use cookies provided by third-parties in order, for example, to improve our performance or services. Some examples of cookies we use within our Websites are as follows:

**Product**

| 

**Type and Name**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
All Products

| 

Analytics Cookie from Google Analytics

| 

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects aggregate statistical data about how visitors use the Websites (i.e., what pages users visit, how long they are on the Websites, how they got there and what they click on) so that we can improve the user experience and serve up the content our visitors find most useful. 

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its analytics service at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) _._    
  
Google also offers a tool that allows you to opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites and can be found [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).   
  
All Products

| 

Advertising Cookie from Google Adwords

| 

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects data about your activities within the Services to provide you targeted advertising, but does not personally or directly identify you.  

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its advertising features at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

You can opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). You can also opt out with [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCjR4sMQxSJOzB_v8TNsRdxQm9IOWavuDzrTGX3ANa8kqL6ITAuvJTz80Gcsh_l-z6OoMveMxAUAhfjoO1OxDTVkXfwPgey3tRsdJsgMeZ6oDRf0Wb8&hl=en) or the [NAI’s consumer opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed).  
  
Al Manhal’s Websites may use social media features, such as the Facebook ‘like’ button (“ **Social Media Features** ”).These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Websites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly.You may be given the option by such Social Media Features to post information about your activities on our Websites to a profile page of yours that is provided by a third party Social Media network in order to share with others within your network. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Websites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the relevant Social Media Features.

**C.    How Do We Use the Information?**

We will use the Personal Information we collect for limited internal purposes that may include, but are not limited to,processing your transactions, establishing the identity of account holders,customer service, development, content processing, content classification,assessing your qualifications for employment, verifying your employment application, and providing you with information concerning our products and services. We will retain this information. We also may use that Personal Information to improve and customize our content.

We may use the Personal Information and non-Personal Information we collect by sharing it with third party agents,vendors, contractors, partners, or content providers Al Manhal (collectively," **Contractors** ") for purposes of managing purchases of our products and services, servicing our systems, and obtaining support services for our businesses. We are not in the business of selling Personal Information to third parties or Contractors, and will share it with Contractors only as we describe in this Privacy Policy. In situations where we provide Personal Information to Contractors, we ensure access is granted to the Contractors only upon the condition that the Personal Information is kept confidential and is used only for carrying out the services these Contractors are performing for Al Manhal. As part of making the determination as to whether we will provide Personal Information to Contractors, we will obtain assurances that they will appropriately safeguard Personal Information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

The Personal Information we collect from you may be transferred to, and processed in, countries other than the country in which you live. These countries may have data protection laws that are different to the laws of your country. Specifically, the servers we use to provide our Services are located in Canada. This means that when we collect your Personal Information, we may process it in Canada or the country where you live. However, when we process your Personal Information, irrelevant of its processing location, we take appropriate safeguards, as discussed below, to require that your Personal Information remains protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may share your usage data related to our Services with our affiliates for purposes of providing or improving our Services. We will not disclose any information about your usage data related to our Services to unaffiliated third-parties, except as necessary to enhance the product experience, service the legal agreement between us and your employer or affiliated institution under which you are provided access to our Services, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our contractual obligations to report aggregated usage data to content providers, or as required by law.

We also reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information if we are required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect or advance the rights,property, safety, or well-being of our company, our employees, customers, or the public. 

We will not use your Personal Information for automated-decision making.

In the unlikely event that all or substantially all of the assets of Al Manhal are acquired, customer information, which may include Personal Information, may be one of the transferred assets unless restricted by applicable local law.

**D.    What is our legal basis for collecting and using your Personal Information? (EEA Only)**

Our legal basis for collecting and using the Personal Information described above will depend on the Personal Information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect Personal Information from you only (i) where we need the Personal Information to perform a contract with you or your organization, (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms, or (iii) where we have your consent to do so.In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect Personal Information from you or may otherwise need the Personal Information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.

If we ask you to provide Personal Information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with your institution, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your Personal Information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible impact if you do not provide your Personal Information).

Similarly, if we collect and use your Personal Information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your Personal Information, please contact us using the contact information provided above.

**E.    How Do We Secure Personal Information?**

Al Manhal has taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure that Personal Information we have collected or will collect in the future is secure. For example, we have limited the number of people who have access to Personal Information, by electronics security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. As a reminder, Al Manhal provides links to third-party websites. These websites may not have the same privacy policies as Al Manhal. We take reasonable care in recommending these websites but we are not responsible for their content or privacy policies. We urge users to read the privacy statement of a third-party website when leaving our Websites and linking to a third-party website.

We always use industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data we receive. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you under this Privacy Policy.

**F.    How Can I Access, Correct, Amend or Remove Information About Me, etc.?**

We want to assure you that you have access to your Personal Information that we collect and store. Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal Information. You may contact us using the contact information stated above to exercise the following rights:

  * Access your data to check and review them;
  * Have a copy of your Personal Information;
  * Demand that we supplement, correct or delete your Personal Information; or cease or restrict the collection, processing, use or disclosure of your Personal Information; the right of rectification will comprise the right to have incomplete Personal Information completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement;
  * Object to the processing of your Personal Information;
  * Receive your Personal Information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have it transmitted to another controller; provided that the processing is based on your respective consent or to execute a contractual relationship or a relationship prior to entering into contract with you; and
  * Withdraw your consent where the Personal Information we collect from you is based on your consent.

We will respond to your request within thirty (30) days of receipt.

If you have granted consent, you can withdraw your consent at any time with future effect. Please address your withdrawal by contacting us using the contact information stated above.

If you are located in the EU, after May 25,2018, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in relation to the processing of your Personal Information.

**G.   What Choices Do I Have?**

We understand that you may not want to allow our disclosure of your Personal Information to our Contractors, or to let us use that information for purposes that you believe may be incompatible with the purpose for which it originally was collected (as permitted by this Privacy Policy) or that you later may authorize. Therefore, you may contact us to inform us that you do not want to permit these uses of your Personal Information. To do so, please contact us using the contact information provided above.

It is important to us that the Personal Information we collect is appropriate and relevant to the purposes for which we intend to use it. We will use Personal Information only in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the person providing the information. Al Manhal will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, complete, and current. 

You may sign-up to receive email newsletters or other marketing materials from us. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may immediately update your email preferences free of cost by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you or at your account settings on our Websites or by contacting us at [privacy@almanhal.com](mailto:privacy@almanhal.com).

**H.     Collection and Use of Information from Children**

Our Websites are not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any personal information to or on the Websites. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us using the information listed above.

If you are a parent and have questions about our practices, please feel free to contact us using the contact information listed above.

**I.     How Long Do We Retain This Information?**

We retain Personal Information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business interest or other legal need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax or accounting requirements).

When we have no further legitimate business interest or legal need to process your Personal Information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your Personal Information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**J.     What Are My Rights?**

Upon request, Al Manhal will tell you if we process any of your Personal Information. Depending on your country of residency, you may have legal rights with respect to your Personal Information.As such, if you would like to manage, change, limit, or delete your Personal Information, you can do so via the account settings or by contacting us using the information provided above. We will respond to your request within a reasonable time frame.

If we process your Personal Information based on our legitimate interests, you can object to this processing in certain circumstances. In such cases, we will cease processing your Personal Information unless we have compelling legitimate grounds to continue processing or where it is needed for compliance and/or legal reasons. Where we use your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes, you can always object or opt out by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you or by contacting us at [privacy@almanhal.com](mailto:privacy@almanhal.com).

**Questions**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our practices, please contact us using the contact information listed above.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We will notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy by posting an updated policy on this page. You agree that continued use of the Websites is an acknowledgment and consent to any terms contained in this Privacy Policy, current at the time of use. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**EEA Data Protection Representatives**

**_Al Manhal Data Protection Representative_**

| 

**_Country of Business Registration_**  
  
---|---  
  
[to be inserted]

| 

[to be inserted]
